Joseph Barnett

https://joescript.netlify.app/

07856865140

Joseph-Barnett@outlook.com

SUMMARY

I work closely with customers on a day-to-day basis to educate them on the outdoors, which I know can improve their health and well-being. My aim is to provide the best experience to my customers in relation to their specific demands. I strive to improve my skills and use my past experiences to better my self. For the past three years, my career has given me transferable soft-skills including communicating with customers, working within a diverse range of teams and consistently producing work that meets company standards. I am now looking for a career in tech and believe the course at La Fosse is my best opportunity. I know the course will give me the skills I need to be successful whilst building on my prior knowledge, enabling me to succeed in any tech environment.

Please look on: https://joescript.netlify.app/ to see my current online portfolio

EXPERIENCE

Outdoor Activity Instructor, 04/2023 - Current
Wyedean Canoe Centre - Ross-On-Wye, Monmouthsire

• Working for Wyedean has furthered my experience in a customer facing role, where I work with groups of up to 16 people, guiding them and sharing useful knowledge whilst keeping them safe and being in control in a high risk environment.

Outdoor Activity Instructor Apprentice, 09/2022 - 04/2023

Freelance - Bristol, North Somerset

 Freelancing as an instructor taught me how to best manage my own time and use my organisational skills to find work and deliver high quality instruction. I was able to build a good reputation across multiple companies all whilst studying full time. It was exciting to see the inner dynamics of various companies and to adapt to constantly changing environments.

Outdoor Activity Instructor (apprentice), 07/2021 - 09/2022 Mendip Activity Centre - Bristol, England

• Mendip Activity centre gave me an introduction to working in a big team of people and taught me to deliver successful and professional activity sessions, all whilst building and maintaining relationships with friends who I am still close with today.

SKILLS

- Strong IT skills, currently learning HTML, CSS and JavaScript
- Listening to others and finding the best way to reach a conclusion
- Calm under pressure
- Great Interpersonal Skills, experience leading group activities with customers
- I always approach tasks with a positive mindset

EDUCATION

FDSC Outdoor Leadership Foundation Degree: Outdoor Education, 2024 University of South Devon College -

Paignton, TOB

Modules and Assignments included:

- Developing Academic & Professional Skills
- Principles of Outdoor Leadership
- Working with Groups in Dynamic Environments
- Environment, Impact and Sustainability
- Planning and Delivering in the Outdoors
- Legislation and Risk

A-Levels, 2016 Churchill Academy and Sixth Form -

- Information Technology Distinction*
- Media Studies C
- Product Design C